<resources>
    <string name="app_name">KickOff30</string>
    <string name="day_1">Introduction to Football Basics</string>
    <string name="day_2">Understanding the Field and Positions</string>
    <string name="day_3">Mastering Ball Control</string>
    <string name="day_4">Dribbling Skills</string>
    <string name="day_5">Passing Techniques</string>
    <string name="day_6">Advanced Passing</string>
    <string name="day_7">"Offensive movement off the Ball "</string>
    <string name="day_8">Vision and Awareness</string>
    <string name="day_9">Shooting Fundamentals</string>
    <string name="day_10">Defensive positioning and reading the game</string>
    <string name="day_11">Defending</string>
    <string name="day_12">Shielding</string>
    <string name="day_13">Set Play Strategies</string>
    <string name="day_14">Dead Ball Skills</string>
    <string name="day_15">Heading and Aerial</string>
    <string name="day_16">Goalkeeping</string>
    <string name="day_17">Friendly Match Day</string>
    <string name="day_18">Tactical Awareness</string>
    <string name="day_19">Faking and Feinting</string>
    <string name="day_20">1v1 Offensive Skills</string>
    <string name="day_21">Positioning on the Field:</string>
    <string name="day_22">Fairplay</string>
    <string name="day_23">Team Communication</string>
    <string name="day_24">Video Analysis</string>
    <string name="day_25">Fitness</string>
    <string name="day_26">Mentality</string>
    <string name="day_27"><![CDATA[Q&A and Ask the Coach]]></string>
    <string name="day_28">Review and Recap</string>
    <string name="day_29">Injury Prevention</string>
    <string name="day_30">Graduation and Next Steps</string>
    <string name="desc_1">Dive into the exciting world of football! Learn about the history, rules, and fundamentals that make this sport so captivating. Gain insights into the essential skills required to excel on the field.</string>
    <string name="desc_2">Explore the anatomy of a football field, understanding its dimensions and markings. Grasp the significance of each area and line on the field and how they influence gameplay strategies.</string>
    <string name="desc_3">Master the art of ball control. Develop precision and finesse in your first touch, ensuring the ball stays close and under your command. Lay the foundation for advanced techniques in the desc to come.</string>
    <string name="desc_4">Unleash your creativity with dribbling techniques. Learn how to maneuver the ball past opponents, using both your feet effectively. Discover the joy of dribbling through cones and defenders alike.</string>
    <string name="desc_5">Elevate your passing accuracy and technique. Understand the different types of passes and when to use them. Cultivate the skill of delivering the ball to your teammates with precision and timing.</string>
    <string name="desc_6">Enhance your gameplay with rapid passes and one-touch interactions. Elevate your team\'s performance by maintaining possession and quickening your decision-making skills</string>
    <string name="desc_7">Learn the art of positioning and movement without the ball. Grasp how to create space for yourself and your teammates to exploit the defense. Develop a deeper understanding of attacking strategies.</string>
    <string name="desc_8">Sharpen your field awareness and peripheral vision. Discover how to read the game, anticipate movements, and make split-second decisions that can change the course of a match.</string>
    <string name="desc_9">Become a lethal goal-scoring threat. Master shooting techniques, including power shots, finesse shots, and volleys. Hone your accuracy and learn how to beat the goalkeeper effectively.</string>
    <string name="desc_10">Transition to the defensive side of the game. Learn how to position yourself to thwart attacks and gain insights into reading the game from a defensive perspective.</string>
    <string name="desc_11">Delve deeper into defensive skills. Understand the art of tackling, intercepting passes, and marking opponents. Develop the mindset of a solid defender.</string>
    <string name="desc_12">Learn how to shield the ball from opponents and maintain possession under pressure. Develop strength, balance, and technique to fend off defenders effectively.</string>
    <string name="desc_13">Explore corner kicks, throw-ins, and free-kicks. Understand the strategic opportunities set plays offer and how to capitalize on them for scoring chances.</string>
    <string name="desc_14">Become a free-kick specialist. Master the technique of striking a stationary ball from various distances and angles, and learn how to bend the ball around the defensive wall.</string>
    <string name="desc_15">Elevate your aerial game. Develop heading techniques for offensive and defensive scenarios, and understand the art of winning aerial duels on the field.</string>
    <string name="desc_16">Step into the shoes of a goalkeeper. Learn about positioning, diving, shot-stopping, and distribution. Develop the skills required to be the last line of defense for your team.</string>
    <string name="desc_17">Put your skills to the test in a friendly match. Apply what you\'ve learned in a real game scenario, working on teamwork, communication, and adapting to dynamic gameplay.</string>
    <string name="desc_18">Deepen your understanding of tactical strategies. Learn about formations, player roles, and how to adjust your gameplay to exploit your opponents\' weaknesses.</string>
    <string name="desc_19">Master the art of deceiving opponents with fakes and feints. Enhance your dribbling and attacking repertoire by learning how to create space and break through defensive lines.</string>
    <string name="desc_20">Dominate one-on-one situations. Learn to beat defenders with dribbles, speed, and skill moves, giving your team a potent offensive edge.</string>
    <string name="desc_21">Fine-tune your positioning for various game situations. Understand where to be on the field to maximize your impact on both offense and defense.</string>
    <string name="desc_22">Embrace the spirit of sportsmanship. Learn about the importance of fair play, respect for opponents and referees, and maintaining integrity on and off the field.</string>
    <string name="desc_23">Discover the power of effective communication within a team. Learn how to convey information, coordinate movements, and make quick decisions with your teammates.</string>
    <string name="desc_24">Harness the benefits of video analysis. Study footage of your gameplay to identify strengths, areas for improvement, and tactical insights that can elevate your performance.</string>
    <string name="desc_25">Elevate your physical conditioning. Focus on endurance, strength, agility, and flexibility to enhance your overall performance on the field.</string>
    <string name="desc_26">Cultivate a winning mindset. Learn about focus, resilience, and the mental aspects of the game that can help you overcome challenges and perform at your best.</string>
    <string name="desc_27">Engage in a Q&amp;A session with a seasoned coach. Clarify doubts, seek advice, and gain valuable insights to help you progress in your football journey.</string>
    <string name="desc_28">Reflect on your 30-desc journey. Review the skills and knowledge you\'ve acquired, and set goals for continuous improvement.</string>
    <string name="desc_29">Understand the importance of injury prevention and recovery strategies. Learn how to take care of your body to minimize the risk of injuries.</string>
    <string name="desc_30">Celebrate your achievements! Receive recognition for completing the 30-desc football learning program and get guidance on how to continue your football journey beyond this point.</string>
    <string name="day_number">Day %d</string>
    <string name="expand_button_content_description">See more or less information about the activity.</string>
    <string name="Top_bar_headline">KickOff30</string>

</resources>